DOCX inspection completed
Report: DOC-000001.docx
Total paragraphs: 343
Non-empty paragraphs: 212
Total tables: 24
Detected headings: 2

Detected headings:
- Paragraph 92 [Heading 2]: STATEMENT OF LIMITATIONS
- Paragraph 153 [Heading 2]: TEST CASES PERFORMED

First 10 non-empty paragraphs:
- Paragraph 24 [Normal]: Version: 1.4
- Paragraph 25 [Normal]: Version Date: 31/Mar/2026
- Paragraph 39 [EvvoH2]: DISCLAIMER
- Paragraph 40 [Normal]: This document is intended only for the use of the individual or entity to which it is addressed. It may contain information that is privileged, confidential, and exempt from disclosure under applicable law. If the reader of this disclaimer is not the intended recipient, you are hereby notified that any dissemination, distribution, or copying of this document is strictly prohibited. If you received this document in error, please notify us immediately by telephone and return the original document to us at the address below.
- Paragraph 41 [Normal]: Evvo Labs Pte Ltd
- Paragraph 42 [Normal]: 28 Genting, #05-07 Platinum 28, Singapore 349585
- Paragraph 49 [EvvoH2]: COMPANY PROFILE
- Paragraph 50 [Normal]: Evvo Labs is a specialist in Information Security. Evvo Labs has earned a reputation for integrity, value, and best practices by providing world-class professional services to clients from various industries, locally, regionally, and internationally.
- Paragraph 51 [Normal]: Established back in 2011, Evvo Labs have since become an established name in arena of professional IT and security service provider in Singapore. Leading corporations, government agencies and financial institutions turn to us for their information systems and information security needs.
- Paragraph 52 [Normal]: Our unique understanding of the cyber threat allows us to evaluate vulnerabilities not just to indiscriminate attack, but also to the most advanced targeted cyber threats.
